Guide to the Amil Gargano papers, 1960-2011 and undated RL.11364
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Amil Gargano papers
1960-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Gargano, Amil, 1932-
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11364
49.0 Linear Feet
Advertising executive with several prominent agencies including Carl Ally, Inc. and Ally & Gargano, in both Detroit and New York. Includes correspondence, corporate reports and policy manuals, pamphlets and other printed material, proofs and tearsheet print advertisements, storyboards and sketches, videocassettes, 16mm and 35mm film reels, optical media (CDs and DVDs), memorabilia and other materials that document Gargano's career in advertising, film direction, education and consulting. Companies represented include Ally & Gargano, Carl Ally, Amil Gargano & Partners, Alabama Power, Audiovox, Burger King, Calvin Klein, Dunkin' Donuts, Federal Express, Fiat, Hertz, Horn & Hardart, IBM, Pentax, Piper Aircraft, Saab, SAS, Shearson Lehman, Sight Savers, Smithsonian Institution National Museum of American History, Syracuse University and Volvo. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into seven series: General and Personal Files; Ally & Gargano; Amil Gargano & Partners; Carly Ally, Inc.; Slides; Print Advertisements; and Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Born, Detroit, 1932; Military 1952-1954; Cranbrook Academy of Art 1954; Campbell-Ewald Detroit 1955 (Group Art Director 1957); Campbell-Ewald New York 1959; Co-founder and Chief Creative Officer, Carl Ally, Inc. 1962 (Change to Ally & Gargano 1977); Visiting Professor, Syracuse University, 1973-1998; CEO, Ally & Gargano 1978 (Chairman 1983); Art Directors Hall of Fame 1982; One Club Creative Hall of Fame 1984; Board, Smithsonian Institution Center for Advertising History, 1988; film documentary for SightSavers 1990; Board, Helen Keller International 1990; founder, Amil Gargano & Partners 1992 (agency closed 2001); published book on Ally & Gargano 2010.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Amil Gargano papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2016.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Arthur Einstein papers; Bates Worldwide, Inc. records; J. Walter Thompson Company Account Files; J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising Vertical Files; J. Walter Thompson Company Competitive Advertisements; J. Walter Thompson Company Domestic Advertisements
Collection Overview
Includes correspondence, corporate reports and policy manuals, pamphlets and other printed material, proofs and tearsheet print advertisements, storyboards and sketches, videocassettes, 16mm and 35mm film reels, optical media (CDs and DVDs), memorabilia and other materials that document Gargano's career in advertising, film direction, education and consulting. Companies represented include Ally & Gargano, Carl Ally, Amil Gargano & Partners, Alabama Power, Audiovox, Burger King, Calvin Klein, Dunkin' Donuts, Federal Express, Fiat, Hertz, Horn & Hardart, IBM, Pentax, Piper Aircraft, Saab, SAS, Shearson Lehman, Sight Savers, Smithsonian Institution National Museum of American History, Syracuse University and Volvo. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States -- Management; Advertising executives; Art direction; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Burger King Corporation; Calvin Klein, Inc.; Hertz Corporation; International Business Machines Corporation; Saab (Firm); Shearson Lehman Brothers; Smithsonian Institution
- General and Personal Files, 1961-2011 and undated; 1
  - Alzheimer's Association--Celebrating Italy, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Biographical information, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Clippings and articles, 1964-1995; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Clippings and articles, 1970-2003; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Clippings and articles--Advertising Age, 1961-1982 (Box 1)
  - Communication Arts feature on Amil Gargano, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1984 October; 8 folders (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1984 October-1986; 6 folders (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1990; 6 folders (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995; 5 folders (Box 5)
  - Directors Guild of America/They Shoot Films, 1992 (Box 5)
  - James Jordan obituary, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Legal release for "Getting Into Advertising", 1985 (Box 5)
  - Letters received (binders), 1976-1990; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Letters received (binders), 1976-1990; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Museum of Modern Art "Peace" greeting cards, undated (Box 6)
  - Publicity file, 1978-1989 (Box 6)
  - Real French Connection cover design, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Sightsavers International, 1989-1991; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Sightsavers International--Copy of Tela Zasloff "Restoring Vision", 1996 (Box 6)
  - Sightsavers International--Logo designs`, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Sightsavers International--Mexico, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Sightsavers International--Script notes, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Smithsonian--Center for Advertising History, 1988-1994; 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Smithsonian--National Museum of American History press kit, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Smithsonian--Oral histories, Sidney Bernstein, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Smithsonian--Oral histories, Tom Black, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Smithsonian--Printed materials, brochures, etc., 1990-1994 and undated (Box 8)
  - Speeches--AAAA Creative Seminar, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Agency overview, undated (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Ally & Gargano annual meeting, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Ally & Gargano stockholder meeting, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Association of National Advertisers, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Carl Ally tribute, undated (Box 8)
  - Speeches--How to Prepare Yourself to Become an Agency President, undated (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Jim Durfee One Club Hall of Fame, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Meeting of the Minds II panel, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--One Club Creative Hall of Fame dinner, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Speech to staff (agency mission and structure), 1985 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Thoughts on Comparative and Humorous Advertising, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--Trinity College/Hartford University: Circle the Words That Best Describe the Way You Feel About Advertising, So-so, Mildly Hostile, Hostile, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Speeches--University of Miami: A Somewhat Candid and Moderately Rational Look at Advertising, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Syracuse University, 1978-2000; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Syracuse University--Marianne Marton dissertation, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Young Latin Americans Series (German Gargano), 1991 (Box 8)
- Ally & Gargano, 1966-2007 and undated; 2
  - Advertising Age agency income report, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Agency history by Amil Gargano, proofs, undated (Box 9)
  - Analysts Meeting, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Audiovisual materials commercials lists, 1979-1984 (Box 9)
  - Cardio-Fitness Corporation employee program, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Case histories, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Case histories, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Client additional case studies binder, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Client additional case study results binder, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Client case histories, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Client case studies binder, 1968-2007 (Box 9)
  - Client case studies binder, 1968-2007; 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Client lists, 1984-1986 (Box 10)
  - Clients--American Cancer Society, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Clients--Bank of New York, 1986-1990 (Box 10)
  - Clients--Binders, 1966-1989; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Clients--Binders, 1966-1989; 6 folders (Box 11)
  - Clients--Burger King, undated, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Clients--Calvin Klein, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Clients--Chris-Craft Aqua-Home, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Commodore, 1982 and undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Dunkin' Donuts, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Fiat photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Fiat, Pan Am (with David Niven) photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Horn & Hardart, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--MCI, 1979-2003 (Box 12)
  - Clients--Miscellaneous materials, 1978-2000; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Clients--Pan Am photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Pan Am photographs, undated (Box 41)
  - Clients--Pentax, 1978-1982 (Box 12)
  - Clients--Pentax Advertising Review and Proposal, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Clients--Piper photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Piper, Cocoribe Rum, Canadair, MCI, 1980-1982 and undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Saab collateral literature, 1983-1989 (Box 12)
  - Clients--SAS photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Clients--Shearson Lehman, 1989-1990; 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Clients--Timberland history, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Clients--Travelers, Theater of Man TV, undated (Box 13)
  - Clients--Volvo photographs, undated (Box 13)
  - Clippings and articles, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Clippings--Print Magazine feature on Joe Sedelmeier, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Clippings--Print Magazine feature on Rick Meyerowitz, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Clippings--World Journal Tribune final issue, 1967 May 5 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1990; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Creative Department organization, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Credentials, 1979-1984 (Box 13)
  - Credentials, 1983-1988; 5 folders (Box 14)
  - DDB--Creation of subsidiary, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Definition of Creativity, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Don Elliott (musician), 1982 (Box 14)
  - Financial, 1983-1986 (Box 14)
  - Financial--Press release, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Financial--Profit-sharing plan, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Financial--SEC materials, 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Financial--SEC Registration Statement, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Financial--Specimen stock share, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Financial--Statements, 1983-1985 (Box 15)
  - Financial Relations Board Annual Meeting outline, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Letterhead, undated (Box 15)
  - Management Meeting, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Memos after MCA merger, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Mike Tesch Advertising Hall of Fame, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous materials, undated (Box 15)
  - NASDAQ materials, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - New Business--Binder, 1980-2006; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - New Business--Binder, 1980-2006; 5 folders (Box 16)
  - New Business--Cantel Cellular (Canada), 1984 (Box 16)
  - New Business--Chicago Air, 1986 (Box 16)
  - New Business--Chiquita, 1985 (Box 16)
  - New Business--CIBA-GEIGY, 1982; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - New Business--Donnelley Information Publishing, 1985 (Box 17)
  - New Business--Duffy Mott, 1984 (Box 17)
  - New Business--E.F. Hutton, 1986 (Box 17)
  - New Business--Electrolux, 1985 (Box 17)
  - New Business--Equitable, 1986; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - New Business--Gulf & Western, 1986 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Harvard Health, 1987 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Hasbro, 1984-1986 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Hershey Pasta, 1986 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Magnavox, 1985 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Molson, 1983; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - New Business--NYNEX, 1991 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Olympus, 1982 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Penn Mutual, 1985 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Pioneer Electronics, 1979 (Box 18)
  - New Business--Publishers Clearing House, 1980 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Ramada Inns, 1981 (Box 19)
  - New Business--RCA, 1984 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Residence Inns, 1985 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Revlon, 1983-1985 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Rolls Royce, 1983 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Scandinavian World Cruises, 1980 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Seagram, 1985 (Box 19)
  - New Business--Shearson Lehman Hutton, 1989; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Press releases, 1979-1987 (Box 20)
  - Print materials, 1984 and undated (Box 20)
  - Promotional materials, undated (Box 20)
  - Public Offering--Ally Gargano/MCA brochure, undated (Box 20)
  - Public Offering--Chiat/Day, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Public Offering--Miscellaneous, 1984-1989; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Public Offering--Omnicom, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Public Offering--Press releases, 1980-1986 (Box 20)
  - Publicity file, 1978-1981; 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Publicity file, 1982-1985; 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Staff biographies, undated (Box 21)
  - Staff jury duty letters, 1967-1980 (Box 21)
  - Staff photographs, undated (Box 21)
  - Standard letter of agreement, undated (Box 21)
  - Summary of recent results, undated (Box 21)
  - Swedish Advertisers Association visit, 1983 (Box 21)
  - United Cerebral Palsy (corporate contributions), 1980 (Box 21)
  - Veronis Suhler report on communications industry, 1986 (Box 21)
- Amil Gargano & Partners, 1991-1999 and undated; 3
  - Business proposal to form agency, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Client case histories, undated (Box 22)
  - Clients--Alabama Power, 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - Clients--American Express, undated (Box 22)
  - Clients--Binder (American Express, Helen Keller, Regional Bells), 1992 (Box 22)
  - Clients--Helen Keller International, 1991-1997; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Clients--Icy Vodka, undated (Box 23)
  - Clients--LCI International, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Clients--National Cable Television Association (now Internet and Television Association), 1994 (Box 23)
  - Clients--NYNEX: President Clinton Answering Children's Questions, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, 1998 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Partnership for a Drug-Free America, 1997-1999 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Peter Peterson, Facing Up, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Shearson Lehman case history, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Showtime, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Clients--Showtime, Assault at West Point, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Clients--Southern Company, 1995; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Clients--Thomas Lucas Productions, Advertising and the American Dream, 1992-1993 (Box 24)
  - Clippings and articles, 1991-1998; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1998; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Creative philosophy/credentials, undated (Box 24)
  - Credentials drafts, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Greeting cards, undated (Box 24)
  - New business, 1998 (Box 24)
  - New business--Astra Merck, undated (Box 25)
  - New business--Bank of America, 1992 (Box 25)
  - New business--Binder, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - New business--Correspondence, 1993-1994; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - New business--Ferrari North America, 1994; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - New business--Mr. Turkey (Bil Mar Foods), 1992 (Box 26)
  - New Business--NYNEX, 1990-1991; 4 folders (Box 26)
  - New business--Presentations, 1993 and undated; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - New business--Pulsar Time, 1993 (Box 27)
  - Office move, 1995 (Box 27)
  - Press releases, 1991 (Box 27)
  - Start-up press and publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 27)
- Carl Ally, Inc., 1966-1999; 4
  - Agency historical, 1967-1977 (Box 27)
  - Association for the Help of Retarded Children, 1967-1975 (Box 27)
  - Auditor report, 1971 (Box 27)
  - Carl Ally Advertising Hall of Fame, 1991 (Box 27)
  - Carl Ally biographical, 1967-1999 (Box 27)
  - Carl Ally GmBH credentials, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Clients--Fiat, 1975; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Clients--Fiat "Italian Graffiti", 1976 (Box 28)
  - Clients--Hertz, Fiat, 1966, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Clients--Pan Am, 1972-1976 (Box 28)
  - Clippings--Going public, 1972 (Box 28)
  - Financial statements, 1972-1975 (Box 28)
  - Publicity file, 1969-1977; 2 folders (Box 28)
- Slides, 1968-1978 and undated; 5
  - Beefeater Gin, undated (Box 29)
  - Fiat, undated, 5 folders (Box 29)
  - Hertz, undated, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Hertz, undated, 4 folders (Box 30)
  - IBM, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--Hertz, Tonka, Noxell, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--IBM, Travelers, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--IOS, Horn & Hardart, Krystal, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--Logos, CBS, Carter-Wallace, Pharmacraft, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--RCA Service America, Krystal, Barney's, Robert A. Johnson, Old Bushmill's, Country Club, Salada, Vespa, SAS, Chris-Craft, Pharmacraft, Cinzano, undated (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous--RCA Service America, Krystal, Barney's, Robert A. Johnson, Old Bushmill's, Country Club, Salada, Vespa, SAS, Chris-Craft, Pharmacraft, Cinzano, undated (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous--Service America, Country Club, Norman Cousins, Peaches & Clean, Travelers, undated (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous--Tonka, Federal Express, Beefeater, Pharmacraft, CBS, Noxell, World Magazine, undated (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous--Volvo, Horn & Hardart, Cinzano, undated (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous--Warner Brothers, Clean Air, undated (Box 31)
  - Northeast Airlines, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Pan Am, undated, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Pan Am, undated, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Pharmacraft, undated (Box 32)
  - Piper Aircraft, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
  - SAS, undated (Box 32)
  - Travelers, undated (Box 32)
  - Various glass slides, undated (Box 32)
- Print Advertisements, 1960-1999 and undated; 6
  - Alabama Power, 1994 (Box 36)
  - Alabama Power, 1996 (Box 41)
  - American Express, 1992 (Box 38)
  - American Express rough layouts, undated (Box 38)
  - The Arrangement (film), 1969 (Box 35)
  - The Arrangement (film), 1969 (Box 36)
  - The Arrangement (film), 1969; 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Astra Merck, 1997 (Box 36)
  - Astra Merck, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Astra Merck, 1995 (Box 41)
  - Audiovox, 1993-1994 (Box 36)
  - Audiovox, 1994-1997 (Box 35)
  - Audiovox, 1993-1996 (Box 38)
  - Audiovox, 1993-1999 (Box 41)
  - Avis presentation layouts (New business), approximately 1974 (Box 38)
  - Bank of New York, 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - Bank of New York, 1987-1988 (Box 38)
  - Barney's--Layouts, undated (Box 35)
  - Bell System, undated (Box 38)
  - Calvin Klein--Original boards and sketches, 1982-1984 (Box 38)
  - Dow Jones "Go Gargano!", 1983 (Box 38)
  - Federal Express, 1975-1979 (Box 35)
  - Federal Express, 1984 and undated (Box 36)
  - Fiat, 1975-1977 (Box 35)
  - Fiat, 1975-1976 (Box 38)
  - Fiat/Lancia, 1975-1977 (Box 36)
  - Fiat--Rough layouts, 1970-1978 (Box 38)
  - Fiat--Type and color proofs, 1976 and undated (Box 38)
  - Goebel Beer, approximately 1964-1966 (Box 39)
  - Hertz, 1966-1969 (Box 36)
  - Hertz, 1968-1971 (Box 35)
  - Hertz, 1966-1973 (Box 39)
  - Hertz--Rough layouts and sketches, 1966-1973 (Box 39)
  - Horn & Hardart (including laminates), 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - IBM, undated (Box 36)
  - IBM, 1967 (Box 39)
  - IBM--Layouts, undated (Box 35)
  - John Santucci Senate campaign layouts, 1980 (Box 39)
  - LCI International, undated (Box 39)
  - Mazda--Sketches, undated (Box 35)
  - MCI, 1979-1986 (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous designs, undated (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous sketches, undated (Box 35)
  - Old Bushmill's, 1964 (Box 36)
  - Northeast Airlines, undated (Box 39)
  - Old Bushmill's Irish Whiskey, 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Olivetti rough layouts, undated (Box 39)
  - Pan Am, undated (Box 36)
  - Pan Am--Storyboard, undated (Box 39)
  - Pan Am, Volvo television boards, 1967-1972 (Box 35)
  - Partnership for a Drug-Free America, 1997 (Box 36)
  - Pirelli, 1976 (Box 36)
  - Pratt & Whitney, 1961 (Box 36)
  - Pratt & Whitney, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Random House/Simon & Schuster--Peter Peterson, Facing Up; Shearson Lehman; Travelers, 1990-1993 and undated (Box 40)
  - Saab, 1988 (Box 37)
  - Saab, 1980 (Box 40)
  - SAS, 1965-1967 (Box 37)
  - SAS, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 40)
  - Southern Company, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Swissair, 1961 (Box 40)
  - Timberland, undated (Box 35)
  - Timberland, 1980-1984 (Box 40)
  - Travelers, 1976 and undated (Box 35)
  - Volvo, 1962-1967 (Box 37)
  - Volvo, 1962-1967 and undated; 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Various, 1978-1992 and undated (Box 37)
    Scope and Contents
    Amil Gargano & Partners; Barney's; Bell System; Center for Advertising History; Horn & Hardart; IOS
  - Various, 1960-1995 and undated (Box 37)
    Last Dark Days; LCI International; Peter Peterson Facing Up; Soldiers of Stone; Swissair; Travelers
  - Various newsprint (American Express, Astra Merck, Saab), 1980s-1997 (Box 40)
  - Portfolio, 1964-1999 (Box 42)
    Alabama Power; Astra Merck; Audiovox; Barney's; Bell System; Fiat; Peter Peterson's Facing Up; Saab; Volvo
  - Storyboards--Bank of New York; Calvin Klein, 1982, 1991 (Box 43)
  - Storyboards--Calvin Klein; Shearson Lehman, 1982 and undated (Box 44)
  - Storyboards--Shearson Lehman, undated (Box 45)
  - Storyboards--Unidentified, undated (Box 46)
  - Laminated advertisements, 1968-1995 and undated (Box 47)
    The Arrangement; Astra Merck; Barney's; Federal Express; Hertz
  - Laminated advertisements (Box 48)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 7
  - Original Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 1
    - Ally and Gargano--Advertising Education Foundation Television Reel: Trinity College, 1990 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-001)
    - Ally and Gargano--Advertising Education Foundation University of Miami: Case Histories, 1991 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-002)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel: 18 spots, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-003)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel master: Current Work, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-004)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency Reel: Classics, More Recent Work, 1991 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-005)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency Reel, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-006)
      Fiat, Travelers, Barney's, Pan Am, Polaroid
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency Reel, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-007)
      Federal Express, Ciba Geigy, MCI, Dunkin Donuts, Saab, Sanyo, Bristol-Myers, Timberland, Jergens, Polaroid
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel version A 7:41; version B 10:10, 1988 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-008)
    - Ally and Gargano--Amil Gargano; Comedian FTG., Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-009)
    - Ally and Gargano--Anti-drug advertising, 1987 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-010)
    - Ally and Gargano--Automotive reel: Volvo, Fiat, Saab, 1990 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-011)
    - Ally and Gargano--Bank of New York Corporate "Listener", 1988 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-012)
    - Ally and Gargano--Bank of New York "Schlimper II Rev", 1990 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-013)
    - Ally and Gargano--Barney's Cassett #2: 9 spots, Undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-014)
    - Ally and Gargano--Brief Review of Current Work, 1981 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-015)
    - Ally and Gargano--Brief Review of Current Work, 1981 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-VHS-001)
    - Ally and Gargano--Calvin Klein: 6 spots, 1982 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-016)
    - Ally and Gargano--Calvin Klein: 6 spots, 1987 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-017)
    - Ally and Gargano--Calvin Klein "Stretching", 1982 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-018)
    - Ally and Gargano--Calvin Klein: 6 spots, 1986 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-019)
    - Ally and Gargano--Cassette 2 (Saab): 4 spots, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-020)
    - Ally and Gargano--Cassette 2 (Saab): 5 spots, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-021)
    - Ally and Gargano--Ciba Geigy Cassette 1: Acutrim spots, 1986 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-022)
    - Ally and Gargano--Ciba Geigy Cassette 2: Acutrim spots, 1986 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-023)